{
  "qBankArr": [
    {
      "question": "(function(){<br/>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;return typeof arguments;<br/>})();",
      "optionArr": [
        "object",
        "array",
        "arguments",
        "undefined"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "var f = function g(){ return 23; };<br/>&nbsp;typeof g();",
      "optionArr": [
        "number",
        "undefined",
        "function",
        "Error"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "(function f(f){<br/>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;return typeof f();<br/>})(function(){ return 1; });",
      "optionArr": [
        "number",
        "undefined",
        "function",
        "Error"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "String('Hello') === 'Hello';",
      "optionArr": [
        "true",
        "false",
        "typeError",
        "none"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "10 > 9 > 8 === true;",
      "optionArr": [
        "true",
        "false",
        "typeError",
        "undefined"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": " var f = (function f(){ return \"1\"; }, function g(){ return 2; })();<br/>typeof f;",
      "optionArr": [
        "string",
        "number",
        "function",
        "undefined"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Number( \"1\") - 1 == 0;",
      "optionArr": [
        "true",
        "false",
        "typeError",
        "undefined"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "(true + false) > 2 + true;",
      "optionArr": [
        "true",
        "false",
        "typeError",
        "NaN"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "\"1\" - - \"1\";",
      "optionArr": [
        "0",
        "2",
        "11",
        "\"11\""
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "new Array(5).toString();",
      "optionArr": [
        "\",,,,\"",
        "[]",
        "\"[]\"",
        "undefined"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    }
  ]
}